Haydn Neese

Email: haydnneese@gmail.com | 918-533-8659 | Kansas City, MO 64118 Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/haydn-neese-676088173/

Github: https://github.com/HaydnNeese

My day to day as a software engineer for 4 years has involved developing a Cloud Platform UI using Angular v14+ and working with Java developers to ensure we deliver a user-friendly experience that will allow our users to manage their cloud environments with efficiency and understanding.

Skills

Technical:

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, React, Angular, MySQL, Git, Java, Cloud Platform Development, Kubernetes, Front-end, Tailwind CSS, Angular Material, GitHub, JIRA, Swagger, Load Balancing, Instance Management, SDN Management, Cloud Storage

Soft:

Dependable, Leader, Strategic, Decisive, Communication, Organization, Active Learner, Problem Solver, Self-motivated, Conflict resolution, Adaptable, Entrepreneurial, Versatile, Observant, Collaborative, Mentor

Title: Scout

Purpose: A ride-service curator; Compares prices and ETA of Uber and Lyft Role: Lyft API integration, Quality Assurance, Javascript Assistance Languages used: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Jquery, Firebase, Bootstrap https://djwasing.github.io/Scout-Project-App/

Applications Built

Title: Happy Hour

Purpose: A restaurant/bar hosting site that connects businesses to their

patrons

Role: Front-end development, handlebar

integrations

Languages used: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Jquery, MySQL, Bootstrap, Handlebars JS, Node https://app-happy-hour.her okuapp.com/ Title: Atlas

Purpose: Secure site to store personal notes you would like to keep secret Role: Using React's component-based system to render a functional card display

Languages used: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, MongoDB, Semantic UI, Node, React https://atlas-secure-info.he rokuapp.com

Experience

SS&C Technologies -

Kansas City, Missouri 09/2019 - present

Associate Software Engineer

I began the job with no experience using Angular but quickly learned how to use it to build our UI components. I've built screens for users to create K8s Clusters, Load Balancers, Access Rule requests, Security Groups, Secondary IPs and instance management in our cloud environment. I've learned much about these different cloud topics as a result. As time has passed I've begun to transition to building APIs with Java -Springboot. I am now a student of the back-end but a teacher and leader on our front end.

Freelance -

Lawrence, Kansas 05/2019 - 09/2019

Web Developer Intern

An internship I joined in May of 2019 that was available by request of one of my personal training clients. Spend each day solidifying skills in multiple coding languages, creating new projects and applications, and helping my mentor with his many personal projects. I bring my willingness to learn and desire to be innovative in everything I do while doing my best to improve the environment of his remote workspace.

Next Level Rising -

Lawrence, Kansas 04/2016 - 09/2019

Personal Trainer

Promptly escalated from the lowest earning employee to the highest earning employee in the company after countless unpaid hours and hard work.

Successfully rehabilitated multiple knee and back

injuries that have changed the lives of my clients Developed a business agreement with a local pharmacy to create a health supplement package and delivery service that provided another avenue of health for Next Level Rising's clients

Fast Fitness Personal Training -

Commerce, OK 5/2015 - 04/2016

Personal Trainer

Developed a reputation locally as a personal trainer with maximum results and affordable prices via advertising and branding Quickly accrued 15 clients that were regularly paying a monthly fee to receive training from the business Learned leadership, dependability, management, and problem solving skills that I can carry with me forever

Education

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp; The University of Kansas, Lawrence, Kansas An intensive 24-week long boot camp dedicated to building full-stack web applications. Bachelor of Arts in Exercise Science; Ottawa University, Ottawa, Kansas

Concentration: Pre-Allied Health